Captioning Provided By:
MTV Networks
字幕提供者：
MTV网络
Are ya ready, kids?
孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
I can't  hear  you.
我听不到你说话。
Kids:
Aye, aye, Captain.
孩子们：
是的，是的，船长。
♪ Ohh... ♪
♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
队长：♪ 吸水性的，黄色的
他是多孔的 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ If nautical nonsense
be somethin' you wish ♪
船长：♪ 如果是航海方面的废话
成为你所希望的那样 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Then drop
on the deck ♪
队长：♪ 那么就放下吧
甲板上♪
♪ And flop like a fish ♪
♪ 然后像鱼一样扑通扑通 ♪
Kids: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
孩子们：♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ Ready? ♪
队长：♪ 准备好了吗？ ♪
All: ♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
全部： ♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
♪ SpongeBob SquarePants ♪
♪ 海绵宝宝 ♪
Captain: ♪ SpongeBob
SquarePants ♪
队长：♪ 海绵宝宝
方裤♪
SpongeBob: ♪ Someday I'm gonna
make you my sweetie ♪
海绵宝宝：♪ 总有一天我会
让你成为我的甜心♪
♪ Not overtly,
but sur-rep-titious-ly ♪
♪ 不公开地，
但过分重复 ♪
Drum solo!
鼓独奏！
Dooga, dooga, dooga, dooga,
dooga, dooga, dooga... Doo.
杜加，杜加，杜加，杜加，
杜加，杜加，杜加……杜。
Doo-doo, doo, doo-doo,
doo, doo, doo.
嘟嘟，嘟嘟，嘟嘟，
嘟，嘟，嘟。
Doo, doo.
嘟，嘟。
Hey, looks like you guys
and gals are done.
嘿，看起来像你们
女孩们完成了。
In all my years
of fry cookery,
在我所有的岁月里
炒菜的烹调方法，
I have never seen such
a lovely group of patties.
我从未见过这样的
一群可爱的肉饼。
Especially... you.
尤其是……你。
Such perfection
如此完美
from your little lettuce hair
来自你的小生菜头发
to your rosy ketchup cheeks
到你红润的番茄酱脸颊
right down
to your mustard smile.
右下
给你芥末般的微笑。
May I call you... Patty?
我可以叫你……帕蒂吗？
SpongeBob, I need
that order of six.
海绵宝宝，我需要
六个的顺序。
Here you go, Squidward.
给你，章鱼哥。
One, and two, and three
一、二、三
and four, and, uh...
还有四个，还有，呃...
five and six.
五和六。
That's it, that's the whole
order, Squidward.
就是这样，这就是全部
命令，章鱼哥。
There isn't a Krabby Patty
behind my back or anything.
没有蟹肉饼
在我背后或其他什么地方。
Uh... Yeah.
呃...是的。
Oh, Patty, a patty like you
哦，帕蒂，像你一样的帕蒂
comes around
once in a lifetime.
来了
一生一次。
I can't let them eat you.
我不能让他们吃掉你。
No, the job must come first.
不，工作必须是第一位的。
I can't let emotions
cloud my commitment
我不能让情绪
云我的承诺
to the sacred fry cook oath.
向神圣的煎锅誓言。
"That which is fried,
must be eaten."
“油炸的东西，
必须吃。”
SpongeBob,
where is that other...
海绵宝宝，
另一个在哪里...
Oh, there it is.
哦，就在那里。
Ohh!
哦！
Where's  my  Krabby Patty?
我的蟹黄饼在哪里？
Right here, muscle boy.
就在这里，肌肉男孩。
It's about time.
是时候了。
I won't let you
do this to Patty.
我不会让你
对帕蒂这样做。
SpongeBob, hand over
the Krabby...
海绵宝宝，交出手来
克拉比...
SpongeBob: Oh, Patty,
I can't let them eat you.
海绵宝宝：哦，帕蒂，
我不能让他们吃掉你。
Your beauty must be preserved.
你的美丽必须被保留。
Amazing.
惊人的。
What are you gonna
do with it, take it home?
你要做什么
处理它，把它带回家吗？
Put a little dress on her?
给她穿件小裙子？
Go out for a romantic
walk with it?
出去浪漫一下
与它同行？
Great idea.
好主意。
I wonder if it's too late to
get a refund from my therapist.
我想知道现在是否太晚了
从我的治疗师那里获得退款。
Enjoy, sir.
享受吧，先生。
Can I eat this one?
我可以吃这个吗？
What...
什么...
Hey, how'd they know?
嘿，他们怎么知道？
I love grilled shoe.
我喜欢烤鞋。
What's cooking there, Patty?
帕蒂，那里煮什么？
Oh, are you kidding?
哦，你在开玩笑吗？
I love crepes.
我喜欢薄饼。
Oh, Patty...
哦，帕蒂……
When we're together
当我们在一起的时候
I feel like we're in
our own little world.
我感觉我们就像在
我们自己的小世界。
Like...
喜欢...
Like nothing
can hurt us.
好像什么都没有
会伤害我们。
Fire!
火！
Fire, fire.
火，火。
It's OK, Patty,
the fire's gone.
没关系，帕蒂，
火已经灭了。
You're safe now.
你现在安全了。
Oh, I better, uh...
Get the doorbell.
哦，我更好，呃...
按门铃。
SpongeBob...
海绵宝宝...
how about another game of...
再来一场游戏怎么样...
tie your best buddy in knots.
把你最好的朋友打结。
My turn.
轮到我了。
Sorry, Patrick...
对不起，帕特里克...
I already made plans to go for
a walk through Jellyfish Fields
我已经计划去
漫步水母田
with Patty.
和帕蒂。
As soon as the little lady
只要小女人
dries her hair,
we're heading out.
擦干她的头发，
我们要出发了。
Hi-yah!
嗨呀！
Hey, ya, SpongeBob.
嘿，是的，海绵宝宝。
You didn't forget
about our plan
你没有忘记
关于我们的计划
to go a-choppin', did ya?
去切菜，是吗？
Sorry, Sandy.
对不起，桑迪。
No time for karate today.
今天没时间练空手道。
After our walk, I'm going for
a rowboat ride with Patty.
散步结束后，我要去
和帕蒂一起划船。
Just waiting for her
to put on her makeup.
只等她
化妆。
You know how long it takes a
Krabby Patty to get ready.
你知道需要多长时间
克拉比帕蒂做好准备。
Well, that makes about
as much sense as
a snake with no slither.
嗯，这使得
一样有意义
没有滑行器的蛇
Patties are put in the water
for eatin', SpongeBob.
馅饼放入水中
为了吃饭，海绵宝宝。
Not for beboppin' all
over Timbuktu.
不是为了一切
廷巴克图上空。
Patty.
帕蒂。
Yeah, well, you two
have fun with that.
是的，好吧，你们两个
玩得开心。
Patty and I have
to be on our way.
帕蒂和我有
就在路上。
I've been replaced
我已经被替换了
by a sandwich!
一个三明治！
Maybe I could meet
a lovely sandwich of my own.
也许我可以遇见
我自己做的一个可爱的三明治。
Yeah, that'll show SpongeBob.
是的，那会显示海绵宝宝。
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ 哦，宝贝 ♪
♪ They may call me a fool ♪
♪ 他们可能会称我为傻瓜 ♪
♪ But I can't help ♪
♪ 但我无能为力 ♪
♪ Our gravitational pull ♪
♪ 我们的引力 ♪
♪ When I stuff you
with cotton candy ♪
♪ 当我给你塞东西的时候
配上棉花糖♪
♪ It reminds me
you're so sweet ♪
♪ 这让我想起了
你真可爱♪
♪ When we go riding,
it's dandy ♪
♪ 当我们去骑马时
真是花花公子♪
♪ The way you hang on
to that seat ♪
♪ 你坚持的方式
到那个座位♪
♪ Ba-ay-ay-by... ♪
♪ 拜拜拜...♪
♪ When I'm with you ♪
♪ 当我和你在一起时 ♪
♪ Our love is
stronger than glue ♪
♪ 我们的爱是
比胶水还坚固♪
♪ Whoa ♪
♪ 哇 ♪
♪ Oh, baby! ♪
♪ 哦，宝贝！ ♪
♪ There isn't anything ♪
♪ 什么都没有 ♪
♪ There's nothing in the world,
I wouldn't do ♪
♪ 世界上没有什么，
我不会做♪
♪ For you... ♪
♪ 为你... ♪
Hey.
嘿。
Let go of her,
you patty-eaters.
放开她，
你们这些吃肉饼的人。
No, get away!
不，走开！
♪ Hi-yah! ♪
♪ 嗨呀！ ♪
♪ Whoa... ♪
♪ 哇...♪
♪ Yah ♪
♪ 嗯 ♪
♪ Hi-yah ♪
♪ 嗨 ♪
♪ Hi-yah, yah ♪
♪ 嗨呀，呀 ♪
♪ Wha, cha,
ja-ja-bah ♪
♪ 哇，查，
哈-哈-巴 ♪
♪ Cha, wah, wah,
wah-ba-wah ♪
♪ 嚯，哇，哇，
哇巴哇♪
♪ Yah, yah ♪
♪ 是的，是的 ♪
♪ Hi-yah-yah-yah-yah-yah... ♪
♪ 嗨呀呀呀呀呀呀... ♪
♪ Patty, you OK, sweetums? ♪
♪ 帕蒂，你还好吗，甜心？ ♪
♪ I'm so... Sorry ♪
♪ 我很...抱歉 ♪
♪ I'll never let you
out of my sight again ♪
♪ 我永远不会让你
再次离开我的视线♪
♪ And I'll always keep you ♪
♪ 我会永远守护你 ♪
♪ Out of harm's way... ♪
♪ 远离伤害... ♪
♪ Yeah... ♪
♪ 是的... ♪
♪ Oh, baby ♪
♪ 哦，宝贝 ♪
♪ Our love is so strong ♪
♪ 我们的爱如此强烈 ♪
♪ That's why
I'm singing this song ♪
♪ 这就是为什么
我正在唱这首歌♪
♪ Ba-ay-ay-by! ♪
♪ 拜拜拜！ ♪
♪ Your looks
are sweeter than honey ♪
♪ 你的样子
比蜂蜜还甜♪
♪ From your pickles
to your buns ♪
♪ 来自你的泡菜
到你的面包♪
♪ It ain't even funny ♪
♪ 这一点都不好笑 ♪
♪ Whoa... ♪
♪ 哇...♪
I'm coming for you.
我来找你了
Oh, no.
哦，不。
Look at you.
看看你。
Don't worry, Patty.
别担心，帕蒂。
I'll take care of this.
我会处理这件事。
There you go.
就这样吧。
♪ All better ♪
♪ 一切都好起来 ♪
♪ Oh, baby. ♪
♪ 哦，宝贝。 ♪
Oh, Patty.
哦，帕蒂。
Do you realize
what this signifies?
你意识到吗
这意味着什么？
Mmm-hmm, that's right.
嗯嗯，没错。
It's our six-hour anniversary.
这是我们的六小时纪念日。
And do you know
what that means?
你知道吗
这意味着什么？
Are you all right, Patty?
你还好吗，帕蒂？
You don't seem so hot.
你看起来没那么热。
Don't fret.
别担心。
I know what'll
make  you  feel better.
我知道会发生什么
让你感觉更好。
A dinner at the finest
restaurant in Bikini Bottom.
一顿最精致的晚餐
比基尼堡的餐厅。
Mr. Krabs: Squidward!
蟹老板：章鱼哥！
Where the barnacles
is our fry cook?
藤壶在哪里
是我们的炒菜厨师吗？
He's been gone all day.
他已经走了一整天了。
That boy's never
been a work shirker.
那个男孩从来没有
曾经是一个逃避工作的人。
We got a crowd of hungry
customers waiting.
我们有一群饥饿的人
等待的顾客。
How should I know?
我怎么知道？
Do I look like
an idiot's keeper?
我看起来像吗
白痴的守护者？
Well... Actually...
嗯……其实……
Well, good day, sirs.
嗯，美好的一天，先生们。
As if on cue.
就好像在暗示一样。
SpongeBob, what's
with the fancy getup?
海绵宝宝，什么
与花哨的装扮？
Oh, I just got gussied up
for my special dinner date.
哦，我刚刚打扮得漂漂亮亮的
为了我特别的晚餐约会。
A dinner date?
晚餐约会？
Well, blow me down, boy.
好吧，把我打倒吧，孩子。
I didn't know you
had it in you.
我不认识你
你身上有它。
So when do we get to
meet the little lady?
那么我们什么时候才能到达
遇见小女人了吗？
: By the way,
is she rich?
: 顺便说一下，
她有钱吗？
She's rich in taste.
她的品味很丰富。
How could  you
possibly date anyone?
你怎么可以
可能和任何人约会吗？
I mean, look at you.
我的意思是，看看你。
She must be blind.
她一定是瞎了。
Mr. Krabs: Ooh, a limousine.
蟹老板：哦，一辆豪华轿车。
Oh, there she is.
哦，她在那儿。
Oh, I can just smell
the money already.
哦，我只能闻到
钱已经到了。
Here we are, darling.
我们到了，亲爱的。
The best eatery in town.
镇上最好的餐馆。
Harold, again?
又是哈罗德？
Martha, I know
what you're thinking.
玛莎，我知道
你在想什么。
It is not me this time.
这次不是我。
Well, whatever it is,
it's disgusting.
嗯，不管是什么，
真恶心。
Let's get out of here.
我们离开这里吧。
Mr. Krabs, Squidward.
蟹老板，章鱼哥。
Allow me to introduce
my date...
请允许我介绍一下
我的约会对象...
Patty.
帕蒂。
Your date's a  Krabby  Patty?
你的约会对象是蟹黄派吗？
Methinks the boy's
really lost it.
我认为男孩的
真的失去了。
What is that putrid odor?
那股腐臭味是什么？
: Oh, it's
the Krabby Patty.
: 噢，是这样
蟹肉饼。
What are you doin' with that
rotten piece o' meat, boy?.
你用那个做什么
一块烂肉，孩子？
This isn't a piece O' meat,
Mr. Krabs.
这不是一块肉，
蟹老板。
She's Patty.
她是帕蒂。
: And we're on
a special date tonight
: 然后我们就开始了
今晚有一个特别的约会
so you don't mind if we get the
"manager's treatment," do you?
所以你不介意我们得到
“经理的待遇”，你呢？
Sorry boy, no can do.
对不起，孩子，我无能为力。
Oh, really?
哦真的吗？
Mr. Fiver says different.
菲弗先生的说法不同。
What was that?
那是什么？
I couldn't hear ya.
我听不到你的声音。
How 'bout now?
现在怎么样？
All right, take a seat.
好吧，坐下吧。
Grazie.
谢谢。
Here you go, my dear.
给你，亲爱的。
A throne befitting a queen.
适合女王的王座。
Oh, good evening,  monsieur.
噢，晚上好，先生。
What might we have on the menu
at this fine establishment?
我们的菜单上可能有什么
在这家精致的酒店？
Well, you should know
嗯，你应该知道
considering the fact that you
work  here, sod for brains.
考虑到你
在这里工作，用草皮换大脑。
Speaking of sod...
说到草皮...
Why don't you get rid
of this garbage?
你为何不摆脱
这个垃圾？
It's starting to
stink up the joint.
开始了
使关节发臭。
Don't say such
a thing, Squidward.
别说这样的话
有一件事，章鱼哥。
Patty's just
a little sick, is all.
帕蒂只是
有点病了，仅此而已。
Wight, lubbie-wubbie?
怀特，卢比比-沃比？
I'll show you sick.
我会让你看病的。
Squidward.
章鱼哥。
What are you doing
with my beautiful Patty?
你在做什么
和我美丽的帕蒂？
Beautiful, huh?
很漂亮吧？
How beautiful
do you think  this  is?
多么美丽啊
你认为这是吗？
Stop it, Squidward.
住手吧，章鱼哥。
Maybe  you  can't
see Patty's beauty
也许你不能
看看帕蒂的美丽
but to me she's the most
gorgeous creature in the sea.
但对我来说她是最
海中美丽的生物。
Well, I definitely see I can't
help the mentally atrophied.
嗯，我确实明白我不能
帮助精神萎缩的人。
Good-bye, creature.
再见，生物。
Pay you no mind to that,
wubbie-wubbie.
别理你，
乌比-乌比。
I will always love you...
我将永远爱你...
Yeah, what is that smell?
是啊，那是什么味道？
Patty?
帕蒂？
Ahh!
啊！
What's happened to you?
你怎么了？
I think I can explain, boy.
我想我可以解释一下，孩子。
There was a time when
I was in love, too.
曾经有一段时间
我也曾恋爱过。
She was a Krabby Patty that
looked a lot like yours does.
她是蟹黄派
看起来很像你的。
Well, maybe not right now,
but you know what I mean.
嗯，也许不是现在，
但你知道我的意思。
She was a firm, juicy,
a warm Patty.
她是一个坚定、多汁、
一个温暖的帕蒂。
And attractive- oh, she
looked good enough to eat.
而且很有吸引力——哦，她
看起来不错，可以吃。
So... I did.
所以...我做到了。
Do you hear what
I'm sayin' to you, boy?
你听到什么了吗
我是在对你说吗，孩子？
Um, not quite, Mr. Krabs.
嗯，不完全是，蟹老板。
Krabby Patties are meant
to be loved  and  eaten.
蟹肉饼的意思是
被爱和被吃。
That's what they're
put in the ocean for.
他们就是这样
放入海洋中。
And it looks like
yours is way past due.
它看起来像
你的已经过期了。
I see now.
我现在明白了。
I see what I must do.
我明白我必须做什么。
Oh, Patty, my darling.
哦，帕蒂，我亲爱的。
Before I do this
在我这样做之前
I want you to know that
I only do it out of love.
我想让你知道
我只是出于爱才这么做。
Well done, boy.
干得好，孩子。
And as a reward
for your valiant effort
并作为奖励
为了你的勇敢努力
I'll only charge you
25 cents for the patty.
我只会向你收费
肉饼25美分。
Employee discount.
员工折扣。
Can I get
a doggie bag with that?
我可以得到吗
一个小狗包？
Patrick:  : Could you
pass the chips, SpongeBob?
帕特里克：：你可以吗？
把筹码传过去吧，海绵宝宝？
SpongeBob: Sorry, Patrick,
we're all out.
海绵宝宝：对不起，帕特里克，
我们都出去了。
Patrick: Aw, barnacles.
帕特里克：噢，藤壶。
Patrick: What am I gonna
do with all this dip?
帕特里克：我要做什么
这一切怎么办？
Patrick.
帕特里克.
What are you two morons doing?
你们两个白痴在做什么？
Waiting to watch
the sunrise... with you.
等待观看
日出……和你在一起。
At 3:47 in the morning?
凌晨3点47分？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
In my bedroom?
在我的卧室里？
We come here every morning.
我们每天早上都来这里。
You sneak into my house
你偷偷溜进我家
every morning?
每天早上？
Uh-huh.
嗯嗯。
It's our favorite pastime.
这是我们最喜欢的消遣。
Ah, the memories we've shared,
right in this room.
啊，我们共同的回忆，
就在这个房间里。
They're all here
in this memory book.
他们都在这里
在这本记忆册里。
SpongeBob: Here we are
on the 4th of July.
海绵宝宝：我们来了
7 月 4 日。
SpongeBob: And Valentine's Day.
海绵宝宝：还有情人节。
Oh, you looked
so cute on Easter.
哦，你看起来
复活节真可爱。
What's wrong, Squidward?
怎么了，章鱼哥？
Do you remember what I told you
你还记得我告诉你的话吗
happens to my brain
every time I see you?
发生在我的大脑里
每次我见到你？
: Story time.
: 故事时间。
Can I tell it
this time, Squidward?
我可以告诉吗
这次，章鱼哥？
Pretty please?
请问漂亮吗？
Whenever Squidward sees us
the storm clouds
每当章鱼哥看到我们时
暴风云
in his brain roll in
and a nasty storm rages.
在他的大脑中滚滚而来
一场可怕的风暴正在肆虐。
So Squidward's happy gland
is forced to take shelter
所以章鱼哥的快乐腺
被迫避难
in the recesses of his mind.
在他心灵深处。
But the happy gland
can't find a recess deep enough
但快乐的腺体
找不到足够深的凹槽
so he gets the flu and has to
stay in bed until we leave.
所以他得了流感并且不得不
留在床上直到我们离开。
Ah-choo.
啊呼。
And that is why I will never,
for as long as I live
这就是为什么我永远不会，
只要我还活着
and throughout all time
and eternity, ever...
并贯穿始终
还有永恒、永远……
French Man: Three hours later.
法国人：三个小时后。
Squidward: And with every
fiber of my being, I know
章鱼哥：每一次
我知道我存在的纤维
that I never want
to see you two again.
我永远不想要
再次见到你们两个。
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
For as long
as time shall stand.
只要
随着时间的推移。
Uh, Squidward?
呃，章鱼哥？
What?
什么？
Both: Ohh...
两人：哦……
Thanks for sharing this
moment with us, Squidward.
感谢您分享这个
和我们在一起的时刻，章鱼哥。
Get out!
出去！
Perfect.
完美的。
Wow, that's a nice one.
哇，那真是太好了。
Thanks for inviting us to
your big fence-warming party.
感谢您邀请我们参加
你的大型围篱派对。
Oh, of course.
哦，当然。
Come have a seat.
过来坐吧。
The picnic's
about to start.
野餐的
即将开始。
Oh, this is so neat.
哦，这太整洁了。
I've never picnicked
on a catapult before,
have you, sponge...
我从来没有野餐过
之前在弹射器上，
有你吗，海绵...
It worked.
它起作用了。
Now I just turn on
the electric fence...
现在我只要打开
电围栏...
Now they'll never get back in.
现在他们再也回不来了。
Let's
do it again.
让我们
再做一次。
Let's do
it again.
让我们来做吧
再来一次。
Can we,
Squidward?
我们可以吗，
章鱼哥？
What? No!
什么？不！
Get out.
出去。
But...
但...
No!
不！
You're going out this door
你要走出这扇门
right...
正确的...
You're not mad at us,
are you, Squidward?
你没有生我们的气
你是吗，章鱼哥？
Squidward?
章鱼哥？
: Squidward?
: 章鱼哥？
OK, then, you look like
you need some alone time.
好吧，那么你看起来像
你需要一些独处的时间。
We'll be at the petting zoo
if you need us.
我们将在宠物动物园
如果您需要我们。
Squidward: Do they have
cute seahorses there?
章鱼哥：他们有吗？
那里有可爱的海马吗？
Yeah, they're
pretty adorable.
是的，他们是
很可爱。
And... And the little scallops
还有……还有小扇贝
that nibble on your fingers
when you feed them?
轻咬你的手指
你什么时候喂它们？
Oh, yeah.
哦，是的。
Can I come?
我可以来吗？
Both: Ooh...
两人：哦……
Yeah!
是的！
Men: ♪ Dum, dum ♪
男人：♪ 嗯，嗯 ♪
♪ Dum, dum ♪
♪ 达姆，达姆 ♪
Both: Good night,
Squidward.
两人：晚安，
章鱼哥。
Hey, Patrick...
嘿，帕特里克...
Did you notice something
different  about Squidward?
你有没有注意到什么
章鱼哥有什么不同吗？
Uh... New glasses?
呃……新眼镜？
No, no, I mean,
he seems... happier.
不，不，我的意思是，
他看起来……更快乐了。
Good night, Bikini Bottom!
晚安，比基尼泳裤！
I love you!
我爱你！
He's probably happy
about his new glasses.
他大概很高兴
关于他的新眼镜。
Ah, ah...
啊啊啊……
Good morning, SpongeBob.
早上好，海绵宝宝。
Squidward: "Honk".
章鱼哥：“按喇叭”。
Squidward, what are
you doing here?
章鱼哥，什么是
你在这里做什么？
You were right, SpongeBob.
你是对的，海绵宝宝。
Watching the sun rise
看着太阳升起
together  is  much  better.
在一起好多了。
Oh yeah, I forgot,
it's the new Squidward.
哦，是的，我忘了，
这是新的章鱼哥。
I guess I better
get ready for work.
我想我更好
准备工作。
Boy, the new Squidward
sure is friendly.
男孩，新的章鱼哥
当然是友好的。
The new Squidward
sure is helpful.
新章鱼哥
当然有帮助。
Ahh... Huh?
啊……啊？
The new Squidward
sure is hygienic.
新章鱼哥
当然很卫生。
Boy, the new Squidward
sure is chummy.
男孩，新的章鱼哥
当然是亲密的。
Ahh... This is more like it.
啊……这更像是。
Just me, my grill...
只有我，我的烤架...
And you, Mr. Smiley face
Krabby Patty.
还有你，笑脸先生
克拉比·帕蒂。
No one can come between us.
没有人可以介入我们之间。
Hello, SpongeBob.
你好，海绵宝宝。
Aren't you supposed
to be out front?
你不是应该
走在前面？
I wanted to help you work.
我想帮你工作。
What?
什么？
Oh, that's
silly talk, Squidward.
哦，那是
废话，章鱼哥。
I'm chief fry cook.
我是首席油炸厨师。
And we fry cook's
work  alone.
我们炒厨师的
独自工作。
And, uh...
而且，呃...
We're not supposed
to get distracted
我们不应该
分散注意力
while we're cooking, Squidward.
当我们做饭的时候，章鱼哥。
Mr. Krabs: Mr. Squidward!
蟹老板：章鱼哥先生！
Stop distracting SpongeBob
and service the customers.
别再分散海绵宝宝的注意力
并服务客户。
How are we today?
我们今天怎么样？
Everything a-OK here?
这里一切都好吗？
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
How's your meal?
你的饭菜怎么样？
Anyone need tartar sauce?
有人需要塔塔酱吗？
I have an idea.
我有一个主意。
How 'bout a free
Krusty Krab Jr. Crew hat
for the little tyke?
免费的怎么样
Krusty Krab Jr. 圆领帽
为了小家伙？
Mommy...
妈妈...
I'm scared.
我很害怕。
Who wants a free refill?
谁想要免费续杯？
Did someone just say "free"?
有人刚刚说“免费”吗？
What's the problem here?
这里有什么问题？
: He, he...
: 他，他……
He asked me
if I wanted tartar sauce
他问我
如果我想要塔塔酱
and then he gave me a free hat.
然后他给了我一顶免费的帽子。
Free!
自由的！
Mr. Squidward.
章鱼哥先生。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
Listen up.
听着。
Me customers come here
我的顾客来这里
for cheap food
and verbal abuse.
为了便宜的食物
和言语辱骂。
And if you can't get it right
如果你做不好
get back in the kitchen
with SpongeBob.
回到厨房
与海绵宝宝。
Squidward, what are you doing?
章鱼哥，你在做什么？
Mr. Krabs told me to help you.
蟹老板让我来帮助你。
So I made Krabby Patties, see?
所以我做了蟹黄馅饼，明白吗？
Besides, it takes
years of practice.
除此之外，还需要
多年的实践。
You'd never be up to it, sorry.
你永远无法做到这一点，抱歉。
SpongeBob, what are you
doing with those patties?
海绵宝宝，你是什么
那些馅饼怎么办？
Oh, these are
no good, Mr. Krabs.
哦，这些是
不好，蟹老板。
Squidward made them.
章鱼哥创造了它们。
They look OK to me.
他们对我来说看起来不错。
But he's not a real fry cook.
但他并不是真正的炒菜厨师。
He is now.
他现在就是了。
Give him an apron
and put him to work.
给他一条围裙
并让他去工作。
Mr. Krabs: You know, he might
be as good a fry cook as you.
蟹老板：你知道，他可能
和你一样成为一名出色的油炸厨师。
Wow, SpongeBob.
哇，海绵宝宝。
You've been employee of the
month a gazillion times.
你曾是以下公司的雇员
一个月无数次。
I wish I could be
employee of the month.
我希望我能成为
本月最佳员工。
Actually Squidward,
in point of fact
其实章鱼哥
事实上
I've been employee
of the month a gazillion
and six times  .
我当过员工
本月数百万
和六次。
Keep dreamin'.
继续做梦吧
Mr. Krabs: SpongeBob!
蟹老板：海绵宝宝！
Yes, Mr. Krabs?
是吗，蟹老板？
What is the meaning of this?
这有什么意义呢？
What's wrong with it?
有什么问题吗？
Mr. Krabs: A smiley face
with dimples?
蟹老板：笑脸
有酒窝？
Dimples?
酒窝？
It was him.
是他。
New Squidward did it.
新章鱼哥做到了。
Mr. Krabs: Mr. Squidward.
蟹老板：章鱼哥先生。
Yes, sir.
是的，先生。
I have one thing
to say to you, mister...
我有一件事
对您说，先生...
Oh, I just love those little
ketchup dimples you do.
哦，我就是喜欢那些小东西
你做的番茄酱酒窝。
You're me new
employee of the month.
你是我的新人
本月最佳员工。
Special delivery.
特别送货。
For this month's
employee of the month.
对于这个月的
本月最佳员工。
I wonder who it could be.
我想知道这可能是谁。
As if I didn't know.
好像我不知道一样。
No, really, who is it?
不，真的，那是谁？
I don't know.
我不知道。
The guy you're looking
for is over there.
你正在寻找的那个人
因为就在那里。
All: Hooray!
全体：万岁！
SpongeBob?
海绵宝宝？
I want you to pull
yourself together, OK?
我要你拉
自己在一起，好吗？
And then I want you to...
然后我要你...
Um-hm.
嗯嗯。
Help me spell Squidward.
帮我拼写一下《章鱼哥》。
OK.
好的。
Thanks, SpongeBob.
谢谢，海绵宝宝。
Party at my house!
来我家聚会吧！
Squidward: Enjoying
the party, SpongeBob?
章鱼哥：享受
派对，海绵宝宝？
Squidward: How's the cake,
SpongeBob?
章鱼哥：蛋糕怎么样？
海绵宝宝？
It's OK, Squidward.
没关系，章鱼哥。
It's a very
OK cake.
这是一个非常
好的蛋糕。
Squidward: I love being
employee of the month.
章鱼哥：我喜欢存在
本月最佳员工。
Oh, so what if new Squidward
is a better cook than you.
哦，如果新章鱼哥又怎样
是比你更好的厨师。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
And so what
if Squidward replaced you
as employee of the month.
那又怎样
如果章鱼哥取代了你
作为本月最佳员工。
And so what if new Squidward
is pogo dancing
with your best friend.
如果新的章鱼哥又怎样
pogo 跳舞吗
和你最好的朋友。
Pogo dancing
with your best friend?!
波戈舞
和你最好的朋友？！
Ohh!
哦！
Stop!
停止！
Maybe you can take my job.
也许你可以接替我的工作。
And maybe you can take my place
也许你可以代替我
on the employee of
the month wall of fame.
关于雇员的
本月名人墙。
But nobody...
但没有人...
And I mean  nobody
我的意思是没有人
pogo dances
with that guy but me.
波戈舞
和除了我之外的那个人。
Now do yourself
a big, fat favor
现在做你自己
一个大而丰盛的恩惠
and get out, bub.
出去吧，小伙子。
You know, Patrick
你知道，帕特里克
maybe I was a little
hard on new Squidward.
也许我有点
对新章鱼哥很严厉。
I mean, he might
be a good fry cook
我的意思是，他可能
做一名优秀的炒菜厨师
and he might have
his picture on the wall
他可能有
墙上有他的照片
but I still have the
best friend in the world.
但我还有
世界上最好的朋友。
I know, I'll go apologize.
我知道了，我这就去道歉。
Come on.
快点。
Squidward,
I just wanna say
章鱼哥，
我只想说
I'm sorry for being so selfish
and yelling at you and all.
我很抱歉我这么自私
并对你和所有人大喊大叫。
I mean, who cares about cooking
我的意思是，谁关心做饭
and pictures on
the wall and dancing?
和图片上
墙和跳舞？
We're bigger than that, right?
我们比那更大，对吧？
So if you're willing
to let bygones be bygones
所以如果你愿意的话
过去的事就让它过去吧
then I'm willing
to meet you halfway.
那么我愿意
半路遇见你。
What do you say, buddy?
你说什么，伙计？
Put 'er there.
把她放在那里。
He's too proud.
他太骄傲了。
Oh, I'll just meet
you all the way.
哦，我刚好会见
你一路走好。
Lay one on me, pal.
给我放一个，朋友。
Hey, hey, I wanna
dance funny, too.
嘿嘿嘿我想要
跳舞也很有趣。
SpongeBob, Patrick...
海绵宝宝、帕特里克...
What are you two
still doing here?
你们两个是什么
还在这里做什么？
:
What are you talking about?
：
你在说什么？
Yeah, what's the big idea?
是啊，有什么大创意吗？
I don't need
this aggravation.
我不需要
这种加重。
Why are you
still standing here?
你为什么是
还站在这里吗？